journalhome.com 2011-05-24

# Journal Home Free Blog Host Privacy Policy - JournalHome.com

## JournalHome Privacy Policy.

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used.  
We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, discussion lists, safelists, and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by JournalHome.com relational networks and properties.  
The following discloses our Privacy Policy. 

### What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" (IP) address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the JournalHome Media Network, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address.  
The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of the JournalHome Media Network, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement.

### What are cookies?

From time to time, JournalHome.com Media Network or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer.  
A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive.  
A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites.Cookies do not damage your system.  
We use cookies to identify which areas of JournalHome.com Media's Network you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible.  
Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement.

You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent.  
If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. 

### How do you use single-pixel gifs?

JournalHome.com Media Network and its advertisers may use single-pixel gif images, sometimes referred to as web bugs or web beacons, to count Web page accesses and gather some general statistical information.  
JournalHome.com Media does not gather personal information through the use of these images. 

### What information do you collect when I register for something?

JournalHome.com Media Network offers access to some services that require registration.  
We may use your registration contact information to send notification to you of JournalHome.com Media Network products and services by e-mail.  
We also may share that information with our clients. Our clients may send you promotional material that is related to the topic of the service for which you registered. 

### What other information do you request?

We may also request your e-mail address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists, or information about conferences and trade shows).  
Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested.

We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy.

When you sign up for an JournalHome.com Media Network discussion forum, directory, or services, your name or alias is recorded solely for purposes of maintaining your own account. This information is not used to monitor your activity, nor is it used to identify you outside the JournalHome.com Media Network.

When you register for a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.

### How is member storage area(s) information and content monitored?

JournalHome.com Media Network does not automatically monitor or moderate member storage area(s).  
JournalHome.com Media Network randomly monitors member storage area(s) for purpose of securing JournalHome.com Media Network and to assure members are adhering to the Terms of Service.

Any illegal or unlawful activity detected is reported to the proper authorities and the member(s) are immediately banned.  
JournalHome.com Media Network may implement scripts or programs which automatically censors content and disallows inappropriate content from being displayed anywhere within JournalHome.com Media Network.

### What information do you collect when I purchase something?

If you are purchasing something from an JournalHome.com Media property, we and any third party provider, need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date.  
This allows us, or third party providers, to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.  
Credit card and e-mail information will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose except as provided in this Privacy Policy without your express permission.

Wherever JournalHome.com Media collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

### Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?

JournalHome.com Media will disclose personal information and/or IP addresses, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

  1. Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on JournalHome.com Media Networks, 
  2. Protect and defend the rights or property of the JournalHome.com Media Network of sites and related properties, or visitors to the JournalHome.com Media Network of sites and related properties, 
  3. Identify persons who may be violating the law, the JournalHome.com Media legal notice, Web site User Agreement, Web site Terms of Service, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the JournalHome.com Media Network or its related properties, 
  4. Fulfill a user's order or request. 

JournalHome.com Media Network uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure.  
JournalHome.com Media Network reserves the right to transfer all such information in connection with the sale of all or part of JournalHome.com Media's capital stock or assets.  
Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information.   
We are not responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information about their users

### What else should I know about my privacy when online?

The JournalHome.com Media Network contains many hyperlinks to third party Web sites.  
The JournalHome.com Media Network also contains advertisements of third parties.  
JournalHome.com Media Network is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party Web sites or advertisers.  
JournalHome.com Media Network does not share any of the individual personal information you provide JournalHome.com Media Network with, to the third parties to which JournalHome.com Media links, except as stated elsewhere within this Privacy Policy, although JournalHome.com Media Network may share general, aggregate data with such third parties (such as how many people use our site). Please check with those Web sites to determine their privacy policy.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others.  
In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

### Your Consent To This Agreement

By using the JournalHome.com Media Network, you consent to the collection and use of information by JournalHome.com Media Network as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

### What is JournalHome.com?

Journalhome.com is a free blog hosts. In simple terms it is where your very own blog will be located and stored.  
But you are in complete control of what will appear on the blog itself.  
In Short, JournalHome.com hosts [**your blog**](http://www.journalhome.com/about/features.php). 

### What else does JournalHome.com offer?

So many [features](http://www.journalhome.com/about/features.php)... so little time .  

  * It's free, and you can make money with your own ads.
  * Well as well as hosting your blog we ensure that the data is backup on a regular basis.
  * We have walls, statistics, plugins and much, much more.
  * We we handle rss for your blog entries and offer a common meeting point for other bloggers.
  * We tell everybody, (we actually ping them), when you update your blog.
  * Because JournalHome.com has been around for a while your blog will be accessible to over 200 000 visitors.

### Can I advertise on my Blog?

Yes, JournalHome.com is an ad sharing blog hosts. Meaning that you can include your own Google Adsense® publisher ID.  
Once you have created your own free blog account you will be able to select the color, channel and much more.  
_The more you blog the better_
